<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>

    <!-- Title Message-->
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome To <b>Bhandara Area</b>\n Tour Guide!</string>

    <string name="timing">Timing</string>

    <!-- City name-->
    <string name="bhandara">Bhandara</string>

    <!-- Place Names-->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="forest">Forest</string>
    <string name="historical_place">Historical Places</string>
    <string name="travel">Travelling Places</string>
    <string name="shop">Shopping</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Type-->
    <string name="veg">Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="non_veg">Non-Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="veg_non_veg">Vegetarian and Non-Vegetarian</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Title and information -->
    <string name="apple_restaurent">Apple Restaurant</string>
    <string name="apple_restaurant_info">
        Cuisine: Vegetarian and Non-Vegetarian \n\n
        Apple Restaurant is situated beside National Highway No. 6,
        at Lakhani. It is near about 13 miles away from Bhandara, Maharashtra.\n\n
        It is multi cuisine restaurant with varieties of Indian Food,
        as well as Chinese food.\n\n
        It is cheap in  price, but it has good quality food.
    </string>
    <string name="apple_timing">
        Working Days : Everyday\t
         11.00 AM to 11.00 PM.
    </string>

    <string name="ranat_bhavar">Ranat Bhavar</string>
    <string name="ranat_bhavar_info">
        Cuisine: Vegetarian \n\n
        Ranat Bhavar is situated beside N.H.06 in Bhandara. It is famous Vegetarian Restaurant for indian food in bhandara.\n\n
        It has good service, in affordable price.
    </string>
    <string name="ranat_bhavar_timing">
        Working Days: Everyday\t
        09.00 AM to 09.00 PM.
    </string>

    <string name="tuli_suit">Tuli Suit</string>
    <string name="tuli_suit_info">
        Cuisine: Vegetarian and Non-Vegetarian \n\n
        Address: At Sakoli, Dist- Bhandara, Maharashtra
        Tuli Suit is a Resort and situated at Sakoli lake in Sakoli. \n\n
        Nagzira National Tiger Reserve is just 13 miles away from Tuli Suit.\n\n
        It has good service, but it expensive in price.\n\n
        Amenities:\n
        Pool, Kids and Family Friendly, Restaurant, Bar/Lounge, Spa, Breakfast.
    </string>
    <string name="tuli_suit_timing">
        Working Days: Everyday\t 24 x 7
    </string>


    <string name="royal_plaza">Royal Plaza</string>
    <string name="royal_plaza_info">
        Cuisine: Vegetarian and Non-Vegetarian\n\n
        Address: Bhandara, National Highway No 6, Near Honda Showroom, 
        Sainath Nagar, Teachers Colony, Ashrafi Nagar, Bhandara, Maharashtra 441906\n\n
        Website: http://www.omsroyalplaza.com
    </string>
    <string name="royal_plaza_timing">
        \bWorking Days : Everyday\t
        \b08.00AM\t to 10.00PM
    </string>

    <string name="kambhoj">Kambhoj Foods</string>
    <string name="kambhoj_info">
        Cuisine: Vegetarian and Non-Vegetarian\n\n
        Kamboj Foods, a multi cuisine family restaurant opened in Bhandara city,
        with crisp modern design, edgy lighting, experienced staff and the tasty food\n\n
        Address: Address: Vidarbha Housing Board Colony, MSEB Colony, Bhandara, Maharashtra 441904
    </string>
    <string name="kambhoj_timing">
        \bWorking Days : Everyday\t
         11.00 AM\t to\t 11.00 PM.
    </string>

    <string name="stop_inn">STOP INN</string>
    <string name="stop_inn_info">
        Cuisine: Vegetarian and Non-Vegetarian\n\n
        Stop Inn Family Restaurant in Sakoli.A multi cuisine family restaurant
        synonymous with delicious food that can satiate all food cravings.\n\n
        Nagzira National Tiger Reserve is just 13 miles away from STOP INN.\n\n
        Address: National Highway No. 6, Sakoli, Maharashtra 441802
    </string>
    <string name="stop_inn_timing">
        \bWorking Days : Everyday\t
        09.30 AM\t to\t 8.30 PM.
    </string>

    <!-- Shopping places and information-->
    <string name="gandhi_chauk">Gandhi Chauk</string>
    <string name="gandhi_chauk_info">
        It is old part of Bhandara city which is famous for shopping.\n
        It is nearly a mile long road placed with various shops in both sides.
    </string>

    <string name="sainath_handloom">Sainath Handloom</string>
    <string name="sainath_handloom_info">
        It is a best shop for providing various types of handlooms in bhandara city.\n
        Address: Ram Madir Ward, Santaji Nagar, Bhandara, Maharashtra 441904.
    </string>
    <string name="sainath_hadloom_timing">
        Working Days : Everyday\t 10.00 AM \tto 09.30PM
    </string>

    <string name="sindhi_lane">Sindhi Lane</string>
    <string name="sindhi_lane_info">
        Sindhi Lane is old part of Lakhani city which is famous for shopping.\n\n
        Address : At Lakhani, Maharashtra 441804.
    </string>

    <!-- Historical places and their information-->
    <string name="ambagarh_fort">Ambagarh Fort</string>
    <string name="ambagarh_fort_info">
        This medieval period fort is situated in Tumsar taluka in Bhandara and
        about 8 miles away from tumsarand 33 miles away from Bhandara district.\n\n
        Fort was constructed by Raja Khan Pathan, the subhedar of Bakht buland shah,
        the ruler of Devgadh around 1700 A.D.\n\n
        Later it came under possession of Raja Raghuji Bhosle of Nagpur
        who used as prison for captives. Later on it had taken over by British.
    </string>

    <string name="bhandara_old_bridge">Bhandara Old Bridge</string>
    <string name="bhandara_old_bridge_info">
        This bridge is developed over wainganga river which is the main source water and fish production in Bhandara District.
        This bridge was developed by British and presently it is opened.
    </string>

    <string name="pandey_mahal"> Pandey Mahal</string>
    <string name="pandey_mahal_info">
        It is a grand structure that has been a landmark for over 150 years in Bhadara city.\n\n
        Pandey Mahal, built by Raibahadur Yadaorao Pandey, was considered to be an architectural marvel.\n\n
        However, Descendants of Pandey have now sold two main portions of the palace, and the buyers have begun to demolish it.
    </string>

    <string name="sangadi_fort">Sandagi Fort</string>
    <string name="sangadi_fort_info">
        The Sangadi Fort is Located at Sakoli Tehsil.\n
        The fort currently lies in ruins erected by the Divan family of Seoni,
        which held the two zamindari estates of Gewardha in Chanda and Rajoli in Bhandara.\n\n
        The fort was called Sahangad or the fort of Sahan, the word meaning the court or small enclosure at the back of a house.\n
        It is said that the village was so named because it lay right at the extremity of the parganas to the south-east.
    </string>

    <!-- Travelling Spots and information-->
    <string name="andhalgaon">Andhalgaon</string>
    <string name="andhalgaon_info">
        Andhalgaon also known as Andhalgaon or the dark village, is a village of 5,164
        inhabitants in 1971 in Bhandara tahsil lying about 16 miles north of Bhandara and
        connected with Mohali by a good metalled road.\n\n
        It is one of the principal centers in the district having a considerable weaving industry,
        silk bordered cloths for women being chiefly produced. \n\n
        The kosa (silk) cloth for which the district is so well-known has become very costly
        and hence the demand for it has correspondingly declined.\n\n
        A weekly marked is held on Wednesdays to which some cattle are also brought for sale.\n
        Andhalgaon has a primary, an allopathic dispensary, a maternity home, a veterinary aid center,
        a sarvodaya center, and a library.\n There are also a sub-post office and a police outpost.
    </string>

    <string name="gaimukh">Gaimukh</string>
    <string name="gaimukh_info">
        Gaimukh, one of the small villages, is located in the Bhandara tehsil.\n
        The village received its name from the rock that resembles a cow’s mouth
        and brings water to the village through a spring,which flows down from Ambagar.\n\n
        Renowned for housing a shrine, the village is frequently visited by pilgrims and
        tourists for viewing a cave temple, which portrays the presence of Kuramvars at the site.
    </string>

    <string name="indirasagar">Indirasagar</string>
    <string name="indirasagar_info">
        Indirasagar dam is an earthfill dam on the Wainganga River near Pauni taluka in Bhandara district
        in state of Maharashtra in India.\n\n
        The dam consists of 33 Nos of spillway gates to regulate irrigation water into the river through out the year.\n\n
        This dam is also known as Gose Khurd Dam because it is situated near Gose village.
    </string>

    <string name="rawanvadi">Rawanvadi</string>
    <string name="rawanvadi_info">
        This place  is famous for a more than hundred year old Temple dedicated to Rama
        constructed by Shri Sitaram Prasad Dube a resident of Gunthara village on a hillock.\n\n
        On Ekadashi Amawasya day of kartik month from hindu calendar, religious gathering takes place here.\n\n
        On the both sides of the tank there is dense forest which has converted it into not only a tourist
        and  picnic spot but also a bird sanctuary.
    </string>

    <!-- Forest and their informations-->
    <string name="koka">Koka</string>
    <string name="koka_info">
        Koka is about 30 km from Bhandara which is covered with dense forest.\n
        The trees in this forest are of the age of 100 years.\n\n
        Koka is a bird sactuary. Here the lake is famous for Siberian migrant birds.
        These birds come in the month of December and return in mid of January.
    </string>

    <string name="nagzira">Nagzira</string>
    <string name="nagzira_info">
        Nagzira wildlife sanctuary is located between Bhandara district and Gondia district of Maharashtra.\n\n
        Nagzira Wildlife Sanctuary is locked in the arms of nature and adorned with a picturesque landscape,
        luxuriant vegetation and serves as a living outdoor museum to explore and appreciate nature.\n\n
        Nagzira national park is category second national park by IUCN(International Union for Conservation of Nature).
    </string>
    <string name="nagzira_timing">
        Safari: 06.00 AM \tto\t 10.30 AM and 03.30 PM \tto\t 06.30 PM
    </string>
</resources>
